<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RPMFy</title>
    <link>https://www.rpmfy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RPMFy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.rpmfy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.rpmfy.com/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rpmfy.com/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Sarvika Technologies is a software solutions company fully committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy by adopting the best protective measures. Come up with any questions or concerns about our practices and privacy policy concerning personal information. You can contact us at rpmsupport@sarvika.com.
This document is an electronic record under the provisions of the Information Technology Act, 2000, and relevant Rules framed there under (as applicable or amended from time to time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://www.rpmfy.com/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rpmfy.com/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This document is an electronic record in terms of the Information Technology Act, 2000 and the rules framed thereunder. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries Guidelines) Rules, 2011, and Rule 3(1) of Information Technology (Intermediary Guideline and Digital Media Ethic Code) Rules, 2021 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms of Use for access or usage of the https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
